Guys, look at that mechanical tower.
It's surreal. It's wonderful.
Hey!
Hey, Marquinhos!
You brought your girlfriend.
Yes, this is Regina.
Nice to meet you, Susana.
Susana, Pedro, Katia.
How are you?
We were talking about Carlinhos' birthday.
I love this story.
Carlinhos is a friend of ours who had a party in the neighborhood.
Manu said,
I'm not going.
Do you think I look like...
You look like a vagabond.
Guys, and Claudio?
Where's Claudio? I've never heard of him.
I don't think he's back from Australia yet.
Claudio is a friend of ours who was very friendly.
He went to Australia, disappeared, blocked everyone.
Do you know who I saw the other day, honey?
Ritinha.
Ritinha is a friend of ours from college.
Is she still with Paulo?
Paulo is already married to Rosana.
Paulo was Ritinha's boyfriend,
but he cheated on Ritinha with Rosane
at Ritinha's birthday party.
Rosana, as far as I know,
she was wanting to go back with Renan.
Really?
Are you still working with Renan?
Yes, but he changed his sector.
Renan and Pedro are working together.
Pedro got a job with Renan.
Did you know he's really bad?
Really bad.
Cancer.
Cancer is a horrible drug that kills a lot of people.
Yeah, but he even went back to his home office job
in Búzios because of that.
Búzios is a city in Rio de Janeiro, close to Cabo Frio.
Is he going to operate, guys?
Look, honey, the last thing I heard
is that he's really bad.
Bad, even though it's a fruit.
It's what we use to designate sadness.
He's really bad.
Guys, let's order the menu.
Let's order the menu?
Friends, the menu is a booklet
that the restaurant sends us
to see the food list.
Marquinho, what the hell is this?
What?
Are you going to keep saying everything,
translating everything we say to her?
I translated...
Now she's pissed off
because I'm translating everything
No, I'm not pissed off, honey.
I just want to understand the situation.
And now he's being passive-aggressive.
He's always like that.
What did you understand, man?
No, Marquinho, Marquinho.
Stop it so we don't keep talking here.
We're here as friends.
Now she's defending him,
something she always does.
What's this?
Where did you get this?
It has nothing to do with it.
What?
Now she's upset
because it may seem like
she's been in a relationship with Pedro for seven years,
even though she's Pedro's best friend.
What do you mean?
Do you have a relationship?
No, Marquinho.
This is Marquinho's joke.
Now everyone knows.
This is something that wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for Tom Climão.
No, seriously.
You can only be mad at me.
Look, did everyone know about this?
Of course.
I didn't know.
I knew more or less about you.
Fuck you, Marcos.
Now he's mad at me.
Cesar, you...
Look, you don't talk to me anymore.
You never talk to me again.
Now she said she wouldn't talk to her anymore.
No, friend.
Now she's yelling.
She's desperate.
Now if it's with Climão,
I'm going to try a conversation.
Guys, what about the fire?
It didn't go out.
But how did he manage to cheat on her?
He cheated on her.
And before that, he had cheated on Renan?
No, Renan doesn't cheat on anyone.
He's the one who cheated on her.
But he...
And...
And Ritinha was cheated on.
In Búzios?
No, there's no Búzios.
Búzios?
Búzios is the home office.
And Australia?
Who was in Australia?
Was it her who was in Australia
while he was in Australia?
Was he cheating on her?
No.
It was someone else who was in Australia.
Búzios?
Búzios.
Stay in Búzios.
Australia isn't in Búzios.
No, but...
What about cancer?
What's wrong with cancer?
Cancer?
Is he having cancer?
Not him.
It's Renan who's having cancer.